Guide to the Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
- National Society of Professional Engineers (NSPE), 1983-1989 (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
- Professors-at-Large, 1971-1982 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Professors-at-Large, 1971-1982 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Submicron Structures Facility- Policy Board, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 12-13)
- Quarterly Publication - Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Criticism Received (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Criticism Received, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Correspondence- Re: Arrangement, 1966-1967 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Correspondence, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Capstones of Century I (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Quarterly Publication -Correspondence, Fall 1971 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Panel on Women (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous Materials (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Correspondence, Summer 1972 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Correspondence, Fall 1972 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Introduction (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Summary Report of the Cornell Workshop on Energy and the Environment, May 1972 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Drafts of papers (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Engineering Cornell Quarterly, Winter 1973 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Graphic Work (Box 39, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, Winter 1973 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- Gardner Paper (Box 39, Folder 38)
- Oliver Paper (Box 39, Folder 39)
- Miscellaneous Materials (Box 39, Folder 40)
- Correspondence, Fall 1974 (Box 39, Folder 41)
- Miscellaneous Materials (Box 39, Folder 42)
- Correspondence, Winter 1975 (Box 39, Folder 43)
- Winter, George (Box 39, Folder 44)
- Capranica, Robert R. (Box 39, Folder 45)
- Correspondence, Spring 1975 (Box 39, Folder 46)
- Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 47)
- Financial Aid Packages: survival kits for students and colleges today, Summer 1975 (Box 39, Folder 48)
- Correspondence, Fall 1975 (Box 39, Folder 49)
- Correspondence, Fall 1975 (Box 39, Folder 50)
- Correspondence, Summer 1976 (Box 39, Folder 51)
- Correspondence, Fall 1976 (Box 39, Folder 52)
- Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 53)
- Susquehanna Fund (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Department of Structural Engineering, 1982-1984 (Box 40, Folder 2-3)
- Study Group for Undergraduate Education (Box 40, Folder 4)
- General Correspondence T, 1972-1990 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- A Program to Enhance the Effectiveness of Teaching Assistants, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- H. M. Taylor (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Theory Center- Site Dispute (Box 40, Folder 8-9)
- University Computing Board, T.E. Everhart, Chairman, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 10-11)
- Theory Center- Facilities Resources allocation Committee & Buildings and Properties Committees (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Theory Center- Deputy Director Search (Box 40, Folder 13-14)
- Theory Center Networking Group- Annual Report, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Theory Center/Engineering Building- Development Plan (Box 40, Folder 17-19)
- Theory Center Building (comments about site, Grumman Hall, etc.) (Box 40, Folder 20)
- ABET, 1987-1990 (Box 41, Folder 1-3)
- ABET Review, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- ABET, 1991-1995 (Box 41, Folder 5-6)
- Academic & Advising Environment Task Force (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Administration, Planning & Facilities - Human Resources, Office of Advising, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Administration Review, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Advising, 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- AEP External Review (Box 41, Folder 11)
- AEP Director Search (Box 41, Folder 12)
- AEP, 1995- (Box 41, Folder 13)
- AEP, 1989-1994 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Annual Reports to Provost, 1989-1996 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Annual Reports to Provost, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Asia Strategy (Box 41, Folder 17-18)
- Awards, Teaching, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 19-20)
- Awards, Teaching, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Awards, Teaching, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Awards, Teaching, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Awards, Teaching, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Beinecke Memorial Scholarship (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Boeing Award Nominations, 1996, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Budget, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Budget, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Budget Planning & Sub-Committee on Employee Benefits (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Budget Policies Committee, Univ. Assembly (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Business Courses (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Cady, K.B. (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Case Nominations, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Case Nominations, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Case Nominations, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Case Nominations, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Case Nominations, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- CCGB, 1990-1994 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- CCGB, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- CCGB Bylaws (Box 42, Folder 21)
- CEE, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- CEE, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- CEE, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- CEE Advisory Council (Box 42, Folder 25)
- CEE Director Search (Box 42, Folder 26)
- CEE Program in Civil Engineering Management (Box 42, Folder 27-28)
- Calendar - Mike Isaacson, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Calendar - Mike Isaacson, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Calendar - Harold Craighead (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Campaign, Deans' Planning Group (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Council, University (Box 43, Folder 5-6)
- Council, University, 1988-1992 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Crowe, Greg (Box 43, Folder 8)
- CS, 1988-1995 (Box 43, Folder 9-10)
- CUBIT (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Cultural Differences, Understanding - Course - Eng 355 (E. Gordon) (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Dake, William (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Case Nominations, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- CEE Review, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Center for Applied Math (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Center of the Environment (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Chair Orientation, New (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Chair Selection (Box 44, Folder 6)
- CHAOS (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Chemical Engineering, Director (Box 44, Folder 8)
- CHEME External Review, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Chemistry (Box 44, Folder 10)
- CHESS (Box 44, Folder 11)
- China-Sci. & Tech. (Box 44, Folder 12)
- CIPA (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Class of 1972 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Class of 1989 Letters (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Class of 1990 Letters (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Class of 1991 Letters (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Class of 1992 Letters (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Class 1993 Letters Sent to Alumni (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Class of 1993 Teaching Award Committee Members (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Class of 1993 Nominations for Department Directors and Chairs (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Class of 1993 Tally Sheets from Nominating Committee (Box 44, Folder 22)
- CNF, 1991-1994 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- CNF, 1995-2000 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- CO-OP Cooperative Program, 1985-1998 (Box 44, Folder 25)
- Collins, Donald (Box 44, Folder 26)
- Columbia University (Box 44, Folder 27)
- COMEPP-Cornell Manufacturing Engineering Productivity Program, July 1, 1989, July 1, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 28-30)
- Craighead, Harold NNF Director (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Dean's Prizes, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Dean's Prizes, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Deans Teaching Prizes, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Dean's Campaign Planning Group (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Defense Reinvestment Initiative (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Design Research Institute (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Development, University (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Digital Equipment Corporation (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Directors and Chairs, 1984-1990 (Box 45, Folder 10-11)
- Directors and Chairs, 1991-1994 (Box 45, Folder 12-13)
- Directors and Chairs, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Directors and Chairs, 1996-1997 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Faculty Reception, 1990-1995 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Faculty Reception, Fall 1996 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Faculty Reception, Fall 1997 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Farrel Corporation (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Financial Plan, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Fisher, G.P. (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Fleischmann, Hans (Box 46, Folder 7)
- French Exchange Program - Agreement with Universities Pierre Et Marie Curie (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Geological Sciences, Dept. of, July 1, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Geological Sciences, Dept. of - COPSTOC (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Geological Sciences, Dept. of - INSTOC (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Gergley, Peter (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Gifts, Report of Committee on Acquisitions & Use (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Goland, Martin - Southwest Research Institute (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Golden Key Honor Society (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Gonzer, L.J. Associates (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Gopal, Prakash, Dr. (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Gordon, Edwiin (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Graduate School Dean Search, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Graduate School Policy Committee - JH (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Graduate Tuition (Box 46, Folder 21)
- Gratz, Industries Inc. - William Gratz (Box 46, Folder 22)
- Greatbatch, Wilson (Box 46, Folder 23-24)
- H (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
- Haddad, J.A (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Haefele, Wolf (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Halperin, Robert (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Hammer, David (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Hansen, William- A. Stucki Co. (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Hart, Edward W. (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Hart, Jocelyn Dr.-Assoc. VP. Human Relations (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Hartmanis, Juris (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Harwood, Warner Estate (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Hastings, Daniel (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Health Services, University (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Herbster, William G. (Box 47, Folder 14-15)
- High Technology Extension Program (Box 47, Folder 16)
- High Temperature Composites (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Hoffman, George Trust (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Holbrook, George (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Holmes, D. Brainerd (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Hotel Administration, School of (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Housing, July 1 1982-June 30, 198? (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Hover, Kenneth (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Hsu, Ping Y. (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Human Ecology, College of- Home Economics (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Human Resource Development Council (Box 47, Folder 26-28)
- Human Resource Dev. Council (Box 47, Folder 29)
- Human Resource Related Transaction Processing Sponser Group (Box 47, Folder 30)
- Human Resources, Office of (Box 47, Folder 31-32)
- Houston Fellowship Fund, Charles Lukens (Box 47, Folder 33)
- I (Box 47, Folder 34)
- Industrial Innovation Extention, July 1, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 35-37)
- Industrial Innovation Extension Service- Quarterly Reports (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Injection Molding Project (Box 48, Folder 2)
- International Education (Box 48, Folder 3-5)
- International Engineering (Box 48, Folder 6)
- International Harvester Company (Box 48, Folder 7)
- International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis (IIASA) (Box 48, Folder 8)
- International Minerals and Chemical Corporations (Box 48, Folder 9)
- International Programs (Box 48, Folder 10)
- International Visitors and Scholars- Student Office (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Ireland, National Institute for Higher Learning, Limerick (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Ithaca College Exchange Program (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Ithaca Gun Facility (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Ivy Deans (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Ivy League Institutions Consortium To Enhance Minority Faculty Development in Engineering (Box 48, Folder 16)
- J (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Jackson, Judy J. (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Jacobs (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Jaicks, F.G. (Box 48, Folder 20)
- Janes, Debby (Box 48, Folder 21)
- Japan (Box 48, Folder 22)
- Jet Propulsion Laboratory, JPL (Box 48, Folder 23)
- Job Inquiries (Box 48, Folder 24)
- Jobs-Deanship Vacancies (Box 48, Folder 25)
- Johnson Graduate School of Management (Box 48, Folder 26-27)
- Jones, Anita (Box 48, Folder 28)
- K (Box 48, Folder 29-30)
- Olin Hall Building Fund (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
- Olin Hall Renovation, July 1, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Olin Hall Dedication, October 17, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Oliver, Jack (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Oosterlinck, Andre (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Optoelectronics Program (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Order of the Engineer (Box 49, Folder 8)
- ORIE, 1987-1989 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Outreach Council (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Oversight Committee on Use of University Facilities (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Pacific Rim Initiative (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Paoluzzi, Alberto (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Parthasarathy, G. Dr. (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Parsons, Ralph M. Foundation (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Petrina, Petru (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Pfau, Ann (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Phillips, Al (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Platt, Lewis (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Pottle, Christopher (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Provost, Deans & Adm. Staff Policy Advisory Committee (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Provost, Senior-Occasional Letter From (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Provost's Office, January 1995-December 1997 (Box 49, Folder 23-24)
- Public Affairs Officer For Engineering (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Public Affairs Records (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Public Service Center (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Quality Council (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Quality Service Program (Box 50, Folder 4-5)
- R, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 6-7)
- Radiophysics and Space Sci. (Ctr. Of) (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Ramin, R.M. (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Rankin, Gilbert F., Jr. (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Raychem (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Read, Don (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Read., W. Raymond-Proposal (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Realization Consortium (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Registrar's Office (Box 50, Folder 15-16)
- Reilly, Philip M. (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Resnick, Sid (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Resource Allocation Advisory Committee (Box 50, Folder 19)
- R.P.I. (Box 50, Folder 20)
- RPI/Cornell- ERC Proposal (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Ruoff, A. L. (Box 50, Folder 22)
- Ruppert (Box 50, Folder 23)
- S. I. Handling Systems- Jack Bradt, President (Box 50, Folder 24)
- Safety Division (Box 50, Folder 25)
- Sears, William R. Lectureship Series (Box 50, Folder 26)
- Shaffer, Janice, Button (Box 50, Folder 27)
- Shinozuka, Dr. Masanobu (Box 50, Folder 28)
- Sill, Ken (Box 50, Folder 29)
- SIP, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 30)
- SIP, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 31)
- SIP Pre-1990 (Box 50, Folder 32)
- Smith, J.C. (Box 50, Folder 33)
- Smith, R.L. (Box 50, Folder 34)
- Mark Spiro (Box 50, Folder 35)
- Steuben (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Stofer, Kermit (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Strategic Plan MIT (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Strategic Planning-Administrative Managers (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Strategic Planning Advisory Board- John Hopcroft (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Streett, William B. (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Streett, William B. Biographical Information (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Streett, W.B.-Research (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Streett, William B.-Resignation (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Students, Special Cases-Douglas Coe (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Students, Special Cases-Matt Fuller (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Huff, Richard (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Students, Special Cases-Michael MacDonald (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Students, Special Cases-Morris Mizrahi (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Students, Special Cases-Neville Rhone (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Students, Special Cases-Ravi N. Sudan (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Students, Special Cases (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Synthesis Coalition-, December 1989-August 1991 (Box 51, Folder 18-19)
- Synthesis Coalition, September 1991 (Box 51, Folder 20-22)
- Synthesis Committee (Box 51, Folder 23)
- TAM 1991-Director Search (Box 51, Folder 24)
- TAM, 1990-1992 (Box 51, Folder 25)
- Tang, C.L. (Box 51, Folder 26)
- TC3-Tomkins Cortland Community College (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Teaching Improving (Box 52, Folder 2)
- TECRO in the US (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Teknekron Communications System (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Telage, Cindy (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Telluride (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Theory Center Exec. Committee, May 1985-May 1991 (Box 52, Folder 7-8)
- Theory Center Fund Raising (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Theory Center Futures Committee (Box 52, Folder 10-11)
- Thornfield (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Thorpe Fund Chemical Engineering (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Total Quality Management (TQM) (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Trip Report (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Tutorial Program, Engineering (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Undergraduate Deans Meetings (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Voelcker, Herbert B. (Box 52, Folder 18)
- VP Finance and Treasure (Box 52, Folder 19)
- VP for Academic Programs (Box 52, Folder 20)
- VP for Academic Programs, Planning & Budgeting-Ehrenberg (Starting Summer 1995) (Box 52, Folder 21-22)
- VP for Planning-Wiesenfeld (Up to Summer 1995) (Box 52, Folder 23)
- VP of University Relations (Box 52, Folder 24-25)
- VP Research, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 26)
- VP, Senior, Jay Morley (Box 52, Folder 27)
- Tesla, Bust (Box 52, Folder 28)
- WISE TCA (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Woodard, Grand, Meng Fellowship Fund (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Wruble, Brian (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Zue, Victor (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Undergraduate Program, Engineering, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Administration, Planning and Facilities (Box 53, Folder 6-7)
- Advising, Interface Newsletter (Box 53, Folder 8)
- AAD, 1987-1996 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Chem. E Advisory Council, 1982-1989 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- ECAC Planning Meeting Wednesday, October 11, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- ECAS, April 28-29, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Engineering College Council, September 30-October 1, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Engineering College Council, April 8-9, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Arts and Sciences Dean Search (Box 53, Folder 15-16)
- Admissions, 1989-1992 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Advising, 1989-1994 (Box 53, Folder 18-19)
- Affirmative Action Council, 1988-1994 (Box 53, Folder 20-21)
- Policy Comm., 1991-May 1994 (Box 53, Folder 22-23)
- Policy Committee Minutes, July 1, 1983-December 21, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 24-25)
- Engineering College Council, October 1-2, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 26)
- Chemical Engineering, 1990-1995 (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
- CLEARS Review (Box 54, Folder 3)
- CLEARS Steering Committee (Box 54, Folder 4)
- President's Fund for Educational Initiatives (Box 54, Folder 5-6)
- Ohart, Theodore (Box 54, Folder 7-10)
- Commission on Undergraduate Education, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
- Composite Materials Teaching Lab, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Computing Policy Committees, 1982-1994 (Box 55, Folder 4-6)
- Conference, Engineering, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Contacts, Printout Form OSP, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Continuing Education, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Cornell Research Council, July 1, 1987-June 27, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 10-12)
- Cornell Society of Engineers, July 1, 1987-1993 (Box 55, Folder 13-15)
- Corning Glass Works: also known as "Corning", July 1, 1983-1993 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Corporate Correspondence, 1990-1998 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Corporate Liaison Committee, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Corporate Relations, Engineering, 1989-1998 (Box 55, Folder 19-23)
- Corporate Relations, University, 1989-1998 (Box 55, Folder 24-26)
- Correspondence, General University, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 27-28)
- COTABA - Cornell Office for Technology Access and Business Assistance, 1994-1997 (Box 55, Folder 29-30)
- Defrees Hydraulics Laboratory - Groundbreaking & Dedication Ceremonies, 1983-1992 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Defrees, Joseph H., 1965-1982 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Defrees, Joseph H., 1983-1993 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- DeLesseps, Tauni (see also Schoales, Dudley N.), 1990-1993 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Diamond, Jared, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Dining Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Directorship - Robert N. Noyce Director of Engineering Communications, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Director Search (NNF), 1998 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Dow Chemical Company, 1983-1990 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Doan, Herbert Dow, 1970-1985 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Doan, Herbert Dow, 1986-1993 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- ECAC, Fall 1997 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- ECAC Member Lists, 1990-1993 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- ECC General Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- ECC, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- ECC, 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 16-19)
- ECC General Correspondence, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 20-23)
- ECC, Fall 1996 (Box 56, Folder 24)
- ECC, Spring 1996 (Box 56, Folder 25)
- ECC, Fall 1997 (Box 56, Folder 26)
- ECAC Agenda & Masterlists, Fall 1997 (Box 56, Folder 27)
- ECC 1997 Fall, ECAC Poll for F1998 (Box 56, Folder 28)
- ECAC Fall Meeting Correspondence, Fall 1997 (Box 56, Folder 29)
- ECC, Statler for ECAC, Fall 1997 (Box 56, Folder 30)
- ECC Meeting Schedule, Fall 1997 (Box 56, Folder 31)
- ECC, Spring 1997 (Box 56, Folder 32)
- ECAC Correspondence, Spring 1997 (Box 56, Folder 33)
- ECC, Statler Contract, Spring 1997 (Box 56, Folder 34)
- ECAC Bio Updates, Spring 1997 (Box 56, Folder 35)
- ECC Report to the Board of Trustees, 1968-1986 (Box 56, Folder 36)
- ECC Report to the Board of Trustees, 1986-1989 (Box 56, Folder 37)
- ECC Report to the Board of Trustees, 1990-1993 (Box 56, Folder 38)
- ECC Report to the Board of Trustees, 1995-1996 (Box 56, Folder 39)
- Economic Development, Office of -, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Economic Development, Regional -, 1995-1998 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Edelsbrunner, Herbert, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Educational Computing, Formerly CADIF, 1988-1989 (Box 57, Folder 4-5)
- Educational Computing, Formerly CADIF - CONFIDENTIAL (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Educational Computing, Formerly CADIF, 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Educational Computing, Formerly CADIF, 1991-1993 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- EE, 1989-1990 (Box 57, Folder 9-12)
- EE, Tang, Chung, 1990-1992 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- EE, Seyler, 1990-1992 (Box 57, Folder 14)
- EE, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 15)
- EE, January-May 1991 (Box 57, Folder 16)
- EE, June-October 1991 (Box 57, Folder 17)
- EE, November-June 1992 (Box 57, Folder 18)
- EE, 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 19-23)
- EE, 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 24-28)
- EE Eastman Shealy Situation (Box 57, Folder 29)
- EISEN (Box 57, Folder 30)
- Electronic Packaging, 1991-1992 (Box 57, Folder 31-34)
- Keene, Jim, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Kelley, Michael C., 1979-1993 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Kennedy, W. Keith - Provost, 1984-1996 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Kessler David, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Kettering Fund, Eugene, 1980-1986 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Khosla, Rajinder, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- King, Kenneth, Vice Provost Computing, 1983-1986 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Kline, Ronald R, 1986-1997 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Kodistschek, Daniel, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Kohlstedt, Sally Professor, 1988-1991 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- Korea Institute of Science & Technology (KIST), 1977-1989 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Korea Institute of Technology (KIT), 1985-1988 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- Korea/Vietnam Memorial Comm. Report, 1990-1991 (Box 58, Folder 13)
- Kornblum, Michael, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- Kyle, William D. Jr., 1971-1989 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- L -, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Lance, Richard H., 1986-1990 (Box 58, Folder 17)
- Learning Skills Center, 1992-1993 (Box 58, Folder 18)
- Leuhigh University Visitation Committee In Chemical Engineering, 1989-1993 (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Liboff, 1992-1996 (Box 58, Folder 20)
- Libraries, July 1, 1982-1998 (Box 58, Folder 21)
- Library Committee Engineering, July 1982-1988 (Box 58, Folder 22)
- Lind, Doug Consultant, 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 23)
- Lyon Agreement (1), 1992 (Box 58, Folder 24)
- Lyon Agreement (2), 1993 (Box 58, Folder 25)
- Lyon Agreement (3), 1994-1995 (Box 58, Folder 26)
- Lyon Agreement (4), 1996-1997 (Box 58, Folder 27)
- MAE, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 28-30)
- MAE: re, director, 1982-1993 (Box 58, Folder 31)
- Mail Log (WHS), July 1, 1989-1990 (Box 58, Folder 32)
- Master of Engineering (GPPC), January 1, 1992-June 30, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 1-3)
- Manufacturing, Center for, 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Manufacturing, Center for, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Manufacturing, Center for, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Martin, Thomas B., 1987-1992 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Master of Engineering (FOOD), 1991-1993 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Faculty Minutes, 1983-1992 (Box 59, Folder 9-13)
- Hopcroft Holiday Party Talks, 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Entrepreneur of the Year Program, 1989-1993 (Box 59, Folder 15)